%d Enchant Issues
%d Gear Issues
%d online
%s restored to %s.
%s set to %s.
|cff00c8ffEnhancements|r: Repaired for %s.
|cff00c8ffEnhancements|r: Sold %d junk items for %s.
+1 Segment Color
+2 Segment Color
+3 Segment Color
Absorbs
Accept
Accept resurrection
Accept summon
Accept to add this contact, or use the menu to decline.
Add Friend
Add Note
AddOn Profiler
AddOn Profiler is disabled.
Addon profiling has been disabled. Reload the UI to stop collecting metrics.
Addon profiling has been enabled. Reload the UI to start collecting metrics.
Advanced Settings
AH Current Expansion
Amount
Anti-Aliasing
Applied %d recommended system settings.
Apply Recommended
Auto Insert Keystone
Auto loot delay
Auto-confirm LFG application
Auto-confirm LFG role check
Auto-fit Window Height
Auto-hide delay
Automate gossip
Automate quests
Automatically confirms the LFG role check using the roles selected below. Hold Ctrl to skip it once.
Automation
Automation & Social
Automation and quality-of-life settings for KullThranUI.
Avant Garde
Average (60 ticks):
Avoidable Damage Taken
Back
Background Color
Background FPS
Background FPS Enabled
Backups are stored automatically when you apply the preset, so you can revert afterwards.
Bar Height
Bar Texture
Bar Width
Battle.net
Battle.net Friend
Battle.net Online
Battle.net Request
Battle.net Whisper
BattleTag Request
Block
Block duels
Block friend requests
Block party invites
Block pet battle duels
Block requested invites
Block shared quests
Blocks
Broadcast
Broadcast Message
Camera Shake
Cancel
Capture Current Enchants
Cataclysm Classic
Chest
Choose a focus area to reduce noise and keep related options together.
Choose which equipment set should be checked and shown in the reminder preview. Leave it on Current Equipped Gear if you only want to inspect what you have equipped now.
Class Colored Bars
Class Icon
Classic Era
Clear
Clear Captured Enchants
Click for a complete breakdown
Close
Close This Window
Combat
Combat %d
Combat plates
Combat rankings, display modes, sessions, bars, and meter layout.
Combat Res
Combat res, gear checks, loot helpers, and repair safeguards for dungeons and raids.
Combat Status Text
Combat Text Animation
Combat Text Background Color
Combat Timer
Completed Objectives Color
Compute Effects
Configure Window
Contacts
Copy Raider.IO URL
Could not change AddOn profiling.
Could not set %s.
Create
Create New Window
Current
Current Equipped Gear
Currently equipped
Currently equipped item differs
Custom Nick
Damage (DPS)
Damage Bar Height
Damage Bar Width
Damage Done
Damage Meter
Damage Meter %d
Damage Meter Font
Damage Taken
Death / Durability / Repair
Death as Warning
Death Details
Death Recap
Death recap unavailable.
Deaths
Deaths Color
Decline
Delete
Depth Effects
Detailed data will be collected during combat.
Diagnostics
died
Disable screen effects
Disable screen glow
Disabled
Dispels
Display Duration
Do not release spirit by accident
DPS
Drag the timer from KUI Unlock Mode under Enhancements.
Drag the timer from KUI Unlock Mode under Enhancements. The tracker background is disabled by default.
Dungeon & Raid
Durability low: %d%%
Durability Warning
Easy Item Destroy
Empty
Enable Combat Res Timer
Enable Combat Status Text
Enable Combat Timer
Enable enchant checker
Enable Equipment Reminder
Enable Module
Enable This Window
Enabled
Enables or disables script profiling. Reload the UI after changing it so the new state is fully applied.
Enchants OK
Encounter average:
Enemy Damage Taken
Enhanced Friend List
Enhancements
Enter Combat Color
Enter Combat Text
Environment Detail
Equipment Reminder
Equipment set
Fade
Fade and Scale
Fade In Duration
Fade Out Duration
Faster Auto Loot
Faster movie skip
Feet
Fira Sans
Font Outline
Font Size
Forces
Forces & Segment Colors
Forces Bar Color
Forces Glow Color
Forces Text Color
FPS Limits
Friend
Friend Note
Friends
Graphics and Sound
Graphics API
Graphics Quality
Ground Clutter
Groups
Hands
Head
Header Font Size
Heal
Healer
Healing Done
Health
Hide Alerts
Hide Event Toasts
Hide Minimap Icon
Hide Talking Head
Hide Zone Text
History Font
Hold Alt %.1f
HPS
Icon Shape
Icon size
Ignore List
IN COMBAT
Interface & Comfort
Interrupts
Invite
Invite from whispers
Items / Loot
Keep audio synced
Keep this section collapsed unless you are actively testing performance.
Key Details Color
Key Level Color
Killing Blow
Last tick:
Leave Combat Color
Leave Combat Text
Legacy Game Options
Legs
Level %d
LFG Automation
Liquid Detail
LIVE PREVIEW
LOCK
Lock Window
Low Latency Mode
Mail font size
Main Hand
Max camera zoom
Maximum Rows
Melee
Melli
Melli Dark
Mode
Move it from KUI Unlock Mode under Enhancements.
Move to group
Multisampling
Mythic+ History
Mythic+ History will initialize after /reload.
Mythic+ Keystones Tracker
Mythic+ Timer
Mythic+ Tracker test started. Use /ktmptimer stop to finish.
Mythic+ Tracker test stopped.
Neck
New Group
No Animation
No combat data
No friends to display yet.
No Group
No Icon
No Outline
No recent allies online.
Off Hand
Offline
Online
Open
Open history after completing a key
Open Mythic+ history
Open one view at a time to keep related options together and make the module easier to navigate.
Optimal FPS Settings
Options
OUT OF COMBAT
Outline
Outline Mode
Overall
Overkill
Pandaria Classic
Particle Density
Party from friends
Peak:
Pending Friend Request
Pending Requests
Performance presets, graphics CVars, spell queue tuning, and live diagnostics.
Per-pull combat timing, live preview, colors, typography, and warnings.
Persistent LFG note
Persistent LFG note text
Physics Integration
Pin Player At Bottom
Player Icon
Players
Poppins
Post Processing
Preview Damage Meter
Preview Enter Combat
Preview Equipment Reminder
Preview history (not saved)
Preview Leave Combat
Profiler unavailable.
Projected Textures
Quest automation, invite rules, group tools, and social quality-of-life settings.
Quest font size
Queue from friends
Quick Join
Raid
Raiders
Ray Traced Shadows
Real-Time Monitor
Recent Allies
Recent allies will appear here when they are available.
Recommended: 100-400ms. Lower is more responsive; higher is more tolerant to latency.
Record Mythic+ history
Recruit Friend
Release in PvP
Reload UI
Remove Friend
Remove Note
Remove raid restrictions
Render & Display
Render Scale
Repair automatically
Repair summary in chat
Resample Quality
Resample Sharpness
Reset All Data
Reset all Enhancements settings to defaults?
Reset Module Defaults
Reset Profile
Reset this submodule profile to defaults?
Resize mail text
Resize quest text
Restored %d saved system settings.
Retail
Revert Setting
Revert Settings
Ring 1
Ring 2
Roles to select automatically
Round Icons
Save
Scale
Scanning...
Search friends...
Season of Discovery
Segment
Select a spell or target
Select at least one role. The game will ignore roles your character cannot perform.
Select Friend
Send
Send Message
Session
Set ready: %s
Set weather density
Shadow Quality
Shoulder
Show Background
Show Combat Text Background
Show Combat Timer Background
Show enter combat message
Show leave combat message
Show on instance entry
Show on ready check
Show only in combat
Show Percentages
Simulated combat data
Social
Some system changes need a UI reload to fully apply.
Specialization Icon
Spell Density
Spell Name
Spell Queue Window
Spell Queue Window (ms)
Spells
Square Icons
SSAO
Status
Statusbar Clean
Statusbar Stripes
Statusbar Stripes Thin
Stop Test
Stores 50 keys per character and imports available Blizzard history. Imported keys have no historical gear or party data. Open with /ktkeys.
Stripe Bar
Suppress Loot Warnings
Sync from friends
System Optimizations: Presets
System Tuning
Tank
Target FPS
Target set leaves this slot empty
Target set: %s
Targets
TBC Classic
Tempesta Seven
Test Tracker
Text Size
Texture Filtering
Texture Resolution
Thick Outline
Timer & Key Colors
Timer Color
Timer Expired Color
Timer Font Size
Timer Running Color
Timer Success Color
Tracker & Layout
Tracker Media
Treat communities as friends
Treat guild as friends
Trinket 1
Trinket 2
Triple Buffering
Typography
Ubuntu
UI Clutter
Unknown
UNLOCK
Usage: /ktmptimer [test | stop | config]
Use Add Friend to populate this panel.
Use guild funds
Use same enchant rules for all specs
Use this block for one-click actions before touching individual settings.
Uses Blizzard combat-session data.
View Distance
View Distance & Detail
Views
Visual cleanup, text sizing, and general comfort options for the client UI.
VSync
Waist
Warming up...
Warning Threshold
Weather density
Whisper keyword
Whispers only from friends
Who
Window
Window 1 - Main
Window Height
World of Warcraft
WoW Friends
WoW Remix
Wrath Classic
Wrist
